Contact

7670939393 (Home) balusavarapu.peoplesoft@gma il.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ balasubramanyamsavarapu-01a87885 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Team Management
Microsoft Excel
Technical Recruiting

Balasubramanyam Savarapu

Senior Analyst at AMAZON DEVELOPMENT CENTRE (INDIA) PRIVATE LIMITED

Andhra Pradesh

Summary

Senior analyst, with 7 years of strong experience in issuing offer letters, exit formalities, Leave and attendance, background check, event management, joining formalities, having knowledge in PeopleSoft HRMS, saap, MIS data management, MIS reports, audits, operations.

Experience

AMAZON DEVELOPMENT CENTRE (INDIA) PRIVATE LIMITED Senior Analyst

January 2020 - Present (8 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana

Business operations, employee transport

Matrimony.com Limited Associate Manager-Business operations November 2016 - August 2018 (1 year 10 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

LearnSocial
MIS Associate
July 2014 - February 2016 (1 year 8 months)
Hyderabad Area, India

MIS reporting

Tech Mahindra
Assistant officer
August 2009 - December 2013 (4 years 5 months)

Education

Genius High School

B.Com, English Language and Literature/Letters · (2004 - 2012)